AMBER OESTREICH

2330 Lexington Ave South, Apt 218 Mendota Heights, MN 55120 United States of America

amber.m.oestreich@gmail.com • +1 651-231-5721 www.amberoestreich.com

LEADERSHIP STYLE

Mix of Autocratic and Participative; strive for perfection in everything and set ambitious goals for self and others

SKILLS

Microsoft Office
Time Management
Leadership
Problem-Solving
Organization
Critical Thinking
Data Analysis
Adaptability
Positivity

BUCKET LIST

Travel to every continent Become fluent in Spanish

Obtain my MBA

Buy a house

Get married

Design a webpage

Travel to all 50 states

Go skydiving

Climb a mountain

Make a difference

SUMMARY:

Experienced business professional with a strong background in leadership and operations. Obtained Bachelor's in International Business in May of 2019 and a Master's of Business Administration in December of 2021. Currently pursuing executive level positions within a corporate or retail environment.

EDUCATION:



ST CATHERINE UNIVERSITY

Master of Business Administration, Management September 2019 to December 2021



University of Minnesota—Crookston

Bachelor of Science, International Business August 2012 to May 2019

EXPERIENCE:



Target—Woodbury, MN

Operations Manager (March 2021 to Present)

- Manage flow of shift to ensure staffing needs are met
- Monitor key metrics and identify areas for improvement
- Department Change Committee Leader
- Utilize Continuous Improvement through daily Gemba



IKEA—BLOOMINGTON, MN

Logistics Team Leader (October 2019 to January 2021)

- Assist in the development of co-workers and peers
- Create schedules to optimize the use of available hours
- Monitor and evaluate assigned space capacities to ensure available stock

Logistics Co-Worker (August 2017 to October 2019)

- Operate machinery to company and OSHA standards
- Plan and implement product locations within warehouse
- Complete aisle maintenance throughout each shift

Self Service Sales Co-Worker (April 2016 to August 2017)

- Prepare space in warehouse for overnight replenishment
- Assist in planning warehouse space for new products